Zunaira Asif

I'm an experienced React.js developer. Passionate and motivated person that focus on delivering scalable, responsive and user-friendly applications by utilizing modern techniques and best practices. Dedicated to constantly learning and face complex challenges to enhance my skills for both personal as well as professional growth.

Contact

- +923034774200
- 💡 Farid Town, Sahiwal
- zunairaasif900@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ zunaira-asif-46b072216/
- https://github.com/zunairaas if?tab=repositories

Education

2018 - 2022

BS (Computer Science)

CGPA - 3.11

Intermediate

Divisional Public School and College (D.P.S), Sahiwal

Expertise

- React.is
- React Native
- Next.js
- JavaScript
- HTML
- TypeScript
- CSS
- Node.is
- Tailwind CSS Redux Toolkit
- REST APIs
- GitHub

Languages

English

Urdu

Experience

React.js Developer

01/2024 - Present

Freelancing

MLPBArmory

https://dev.mlpbarmory.com/

- Worked on minting portal for a Next.js website and some email templates.
- · Fixed responsiveness issues and other bugs.

Finarch

https://finarch.co/

- Built an architect website with React.js using MUI and is fully responsive.
- Integrated API's.

Ghoomo Phiroo Pakistan

https://gpp.codeminer.co/

• Developed admin panel for GPP using React.js and integrated API's.

React.js Developer

10/2022 - 12/2023

AltCode Labs

AltCodeLabs

https://altcodelabs.com/

- Developed company's website in Next.js using MUI with full responsiveness.
- Implemented 3D animations using Framer motion and Sketchfab.

Fitcy Health

https://fitcyhealth.com/

- Fitcy health is a **React.js** web app serves as Mental Health Care platform.
- · Implemented all API's.
- Fixed many UI bugs using Grommet library.

React.js Intern

07/2022 - 09/2022

Global Software Consulting

Global Software Consulting

https://www.gsoftconsulting.com/

- Built GSoft website in Next.js with 100% SEO and reusable components.
- · Worked with MUI to fully match flexible Figma design.

Obenan

https://obenan.com/

- · A Digital Marketing website built using React.js where different companies register themselves for local SEO purpose.
- Performed API calls.
- · Worked on UI bugs fixing on user dashboard.